<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>tox@box</title>
    <link>https://pwnedbytoxic.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on tox@box</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 23:10:05 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pwnedbytoxic.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://pwnedbytoxic.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 14:45:33 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pwnedbytoxic.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>Contact Me Feel free to reach out and connect with me through the following platforms:
 Instagram: @damon.hoody Snapchat: @prod.toxic TryHackMe: toxic.sec Hack The Box: toxicsec GitHub: pwnedbytoxic Email: hoody.damon@gmail.com Secure Email: tech.toxic@proton.me  Whether you want to chat about cybersecurity/networking, share your experiences, or have any questions, I&amp;rsquo;m here to connect with you. Don&amp;rsquo;t hesitate to send a message or follow me on these platforms. I look forward to engaging with the IT community!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>THM Writeup | Internal (Hard)</title>
      <link>https://pwnedbytoxic.github.io/posts/internal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 23:10:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pwnedbytoxic.github.io/posts/internal/</guid>
      <description>Introduction/Overview   Challenge Name: TryHackMe Category: Penetration Testing Challenge Points: 60 Author: TheMayor Description: Complex Linux &amp;amp; Docker exploitation without the usage of metasploit (usage of CVE-2021-4034).  Scanning/Recon  IP Address: 10.10.174.253  Inital scan with nmap -p- 10.10.174.253 and later nmap -A -p 22,80, resulting in
PORT STATE SERVICE 22/tcp open ssh 80/tcp open http 22/tcp open ssh OpenSSH 7.6p1 Ubuntu 4ubuntu0.3 (Ubuntu Linux; protocol 2.0) | ssh-hostkey: | 2048 6efaefbef65f98b9597bf78eb9c5621e (RSA) | 256 ed64ed33e5c93058ba23040d14eb30e9 (ECDSA) |_ 256 b07f7f7b5262622a60d43d36fa89eeff (ED25519) Service Info: OS: Linux; CPE: cpe:/o:linux:linux_kernel 80/tcp open http Apache httpd 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://pwnedbytoxic.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 15:28:21 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pwnedbytoxic.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>About Damon Hoody (aka toxic) Hey there! 👋 I&amp;rsquo;m Damon Hoody, also known as &amp;ldquo;toxic,&amp;rdquo; and I&amp;rsquo;m your friendly neighborhood cybersecurity enthusiast, CTF (Capture The Flag) player, and dedicated student at the Computer Networking Academy of Cuyahoga Valley Career Center. 🌐💻
🔐 Cybersecurity Enthusiast: I&amp;rsquo;m passionate about all things cybersecurity and constantly exploring the ever-evolving world of digital security. From ethical hacking to threat analysis, I&amp;rsquo;m on a mission to keep the digital realm safe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome!</title>
      <link>https://pwnedbytoxic.github.io/posts/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 14:55:42 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pwnedbytoxic.github.io/posts/welcome/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to tox@box Welcome to tox@box, my personal blog and writeup library wherein we explore &amp;amp; expose the vast knowledge pool of cybersecurity.
About tox@box At tox@box, I&amp;rsquo;m on a mission to make the internet a safer place, one byte at a time. I&amp;rsquo;m Damon Hoody (aka &amp;ldquo;toxic&amp;rdquo;), your host, and guide through the exciting and ever-evolving landscape of cybersecurity.
What is Cybersecurity? Cybersecurity is the practice of protecting digital systems, networks, and data from malicious attacks, unauthorized access, and data breaches.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
